JERIC NISPEROS

Contact:

Email: jericrnisperos@gmail.com

Website: jnisperos.space Linkedin: Click Me

Summary

Experienced in **Software Engineering** for **1 year** and **E-Commerce and Telco Customer Support** for **4 years**. Committed to delivering exceptional support services to clients and customers in the United States, United Kingdom, and Canada. Proficient in providing top-notch assistance through various communication channels, including Phone, email, and chat.

I am currently a **Co-Owner** and the **Senior Development Manager** of a Gaming Community with **16000 users**. My day-to-day tasks involve adding exciting new features, ensuring a smooth setup, resolving any bugs that arise, and implementing unique gameplay elements that enhance the overall player experience. I take great pride in actively listening to our community's feedback and utilizing my skills to create captivating gaming experiences that keep our users engaged and entertained.

Work Experiences (5 Years)

Norima Technologies Inc. (Software Engineer / Consultant) (FinTech) - Jan 2022 - Mar 2023

- Proficient in a variety of tools and programming languages including: .Net | C# | Jira | Angular | Swagger | MSSQL | Azure
- Adept at utilizing Agile methodologies to effectively manage and complete tasks, ensuring timely delivery and quality results.
- Experience in collaborating with cross-functional teams to share knowledge, generate new ideas, and implement best practices
 to achieve project objectives.
- Skilled in developing clean, efficient, and well-documented code that adheres to industry standards and best practices.
- Constantly striving to exceed expectations by providing the best possible solutions to enhance product capabilities, while continuously learning and staying up-to-date with the latest technologies and trends.

AFNI Company (Chat Support Professional) (Verizon) - Oct 2019 - Nov 2021

- Handling customer inquiries and providing prompt and professional support via chat for a leading telecommunications company in the United States.
- Verifying and processing customer orders, ensuring timely fulfillment and following up on any issues that may arise.
- Assisting customers with basic technical troubleshooting and providing guidance on product usage and features.
- Managing credit/debit card payments, invoicing, and other financial transactions for customer accounts.
- Identifying customer needs and recommending appropriate service options, as well as up selling subscription plans and special offers
- Maintaining accurate and up-to-date customer records and providing regular reports on customer interactions and support metrics.
- Continuously striving to improve customer satisfaction by providing the best customer.

Alorica Teleservices Inc. (Customer Multi-support Specialist) (Amazon) - Sept 2017 - Oct 2019

- Trained in providing phone, email, and chat support for customers in the United States and United Kingdom for a leading retail company.
- Proficient in verifying and processing customer orders, ensuring timely fulfillment and following up on any issues that may arise.
- Skilled in providing basic technical troubleshooting and guidance on product usage and features to customers.
- Experienced in managing credit/debit card payments, invoicing, and other financial transactions for customer accounts.
- Adept at identifying customer needs and recommending appropriate service options, as well as up selling subscription plans and special offers.
- Strong communication skills and ability to promote company's services and special offers to customers.

| Educational Background | Tech Stacks | | |
|--|-------------|--------|-------------|
| Bachelor of Science in Information Systems (2013-2017) | HTML | CSS | Javascript |
| School: Don Mariano Marcos Memorial State University - North La Union Campus | ReactJs | NextJs | AngularJs |
| Thesis Title: Collection and Disbursement Record Management System for Sericulture | ExpressJs | Axios | NodeJs |
| Research and Development Institute (CDRMSSRDI). | C# | MySQL | TailwindCSS |

Certifications

- ► ReactJs Assessment LinkedIn Skills Assessment (2023)
- ► Six Sigma Certification White Belt Certificate (2023)
- ► Front-End Assessment LinkedIn Skills Assessment (2022)
- ► Pre-employment Seminar Workshop (2017)
- ► Seminar Workshop on Computer Hardware Servicing (2016)
- ► Seminar Workshop of Enhancing the Research/Thesis Writing/Teaching Capabilities of RDE Practitioners and Special Science School Teachers (2016)
- Regional Information Technology Research Conference 2016
- ► WIWAG Business Week (2015)
- ► Seminar on Information Technology Business Process Management (2015)
- ► 4th Philippine Society Information Technology Educators (2015)

Soft Skills

- Strong verbal and written communication abilities.
- Proficient in time management and organization.
- Adept in using various computer programs and technologies.
- Ability to handle multiple tasks simultaneously meet deadlines.
- Ability to work effectively under pressure in fast-paced environments.
- Proven ability to work both independently and as part of a team.
- Strong analytical and problem-solving skills.
- Proven ability to make sound and timely decisions.